<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>game on 土叔分享</title><link>https://www.tushushare.com/tags/game/</link><description>Recent content in game on 土叔分享</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:00:01 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.tushushare.com/tags/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>《Mecha BREAK》 Connection Failed to Entry Server? One Simple Fix</title><link>https://www.tushushare.com/categories/games/mechabreak-black-screen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:00:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.tushushare.com/categories/games/mechabreak-black-screen/</guid><description>《Mecha BREAK》 is an extremely fun shooting game that has attracted a large number of players. However, you may encounter disconnection or black screen issues while playing the game. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, here are several solutions.
Firstly, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your computer system for a long time, it may lead to a low system version, causing compatibility issues and thus resulting in disconnection or black screen. You can manually update your computer system, which can easily solve the problem.
Secondly, disconnection and black screen may be due to conflicts between some software on your computer and the game.</description></item><item><title>《Mecha BREAK》 Connection Failed to Entry Server? One Simple Fix</title><link>https://www.tushushare.com/categories/games/mechabreak-server-failed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:00:01 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.tushushare.com/categories/games/mechabreak-server-failed/</guid><description>《Mecha BREAK》 is a popular Chinese mecha game beloved by players. However, some users recently encountered a &amp;ldquo;Failed to Connect to Entry Server&amp;rdquo; error during Steam testing.
Don’t panic—here are proven solutions:
Check Your Network Stability Unstable connections or high latency can cause communication failures. Verify your internet speed and stability. If you’re on Wi-Fi, switch to a wired connection—this often boosts speed, reduces lag, and resolves network-related issues. Avoid Server Overload Server congestion may trigger errors. Try switching to a less crowded server (if available) to see if the problem resolves.</description></item></channel></rss>